https://www.service-architecture.com/privacy_policy.html

Service Architecture
Privacy Policy - Updated April 28, 2020
Overview
This website does not collect personally identifiable information.
Disclosure Regarding Third-Party Vendors
Third-party vendors use cookies
provide services on this website.
Barry & Associates, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices, use of their cookies, or the content of such websites. Also see the Cookie Policy for this website.
Google Display Advertising
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on your visit to this website and/or other websites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Google Ads Settings.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics. Google Analytics gathers information about the use of our website by means of cookies. The information gathered is used to create reports about the use of our website. More on Google's use of information and Google's Privacy Policy.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Barry & Associates, Inc. is
not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy may be updated from time to time. The date of the most recent revision
appears on the top of this page.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact
.
Published by: Barry & Associates, Inc.
Copyright © 2000 -
2020
Barry & Associates, Inc. All Rights Reserved. Privacy Policy Cookie Policy
Application Program Interfaces (APIs)
Models and Metamodels
Business Process Modeling Language (BPML)
Business Process Modeling Notation (BPMN)
Common Warehouse Metamodel (CWM)
Meta-Object Facility (MOF)
Unified Modeling Language (UML)
XML Metadata Interchange (XMI)
Model Driven Architecture (MDA)
Web Services Component Model (WSCM)
Web Services Resource Framework (WSRF)
WS Choreography Model
Repository
Directory Services Markup Language (DSML)
ebXML Registry
Universal Description, Discovery, and Integration (UDDI)
Messaging
Messaging Components
Web Services Adapters
Web Services Message Routers
Enterprise Service Bus (ESB)
Messaging Specifications
Asynchronous Application Service Protocol (ASAP) for SOAP
Message Service Specification (MSS)
JavaScript Object Notation (JSON)
Representational State Transfer (REST)
RosettaNet Business Message
SOAP
Web Distributed Data Exchange (WDDX)
Web Services Addressing (WS-Addressing)
Web Services Eventing (WS-Eventing)
Web Services Notification (WSN)
Web Services Reliability (WS-Reliability)
Web Services Reliable Messaging (WS-ReliableMessaging)
XML Protocol (XMLP)
Blocks Extensible Exchange Protocol (BEEP)
Transaction Specifications
Web Services AtomicTransaction (WS-AtomicTransaction)
Web Services BusinessActivity (WS-BusinessActivity)
Web Services Coordination (WS-Coordination)
Service
Web Services Description Language (WSDL)
Web Services Dynamic Discovery (WS-Discovery)
Web Services Endpoint Language (WSEL)
Web Services Metadata Exchange (WS-MetaDataExchange)
Web Services Policy (WS-Policy)
Security and Authorization
eXtensible Access Control Markup Language (XACML)
eXtensible rights Markup Language (XrML)
Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML)
Service Provisioning Markup Language (SPML)
Web Services Security (WSS)
Public Key Infrastructure (PKI)
XML Encryption
XML Signature
XML Common Biometric Format (XCBF)
XML Key Management Specification (XKMS)
Federated Network Identity
Identity Federation Framework (ID-FF)
Identity Service Interface Specification (ID-SIS)
Identity Web Services Framework (ID-WSF)
User Interface
User Interface Markup Language (UIML)
Web Services Experience Language (WSXL)
Web Services for Interactive Applications (WSIA)
Web Services for Remote Portals (WSRP)
Web Services User Interface (WSUI)
Workflow
Business Centric Methodology (BCM)
Business Process Execution Language (BPEL)
Business Process Query Language (BPQL)
Business Process Specification Schema (BPSS)
Business Transaction Protocol (BTP)
Collaboration Protocol Profile/Agreement (CPP/A)
Common Alerting Protocol (CAP)
Content Assembly Mechanism (CAM)
Partner Interface Process (PIP)
PIP Directory
RosettaNet dictionaries
RosettaNet Implementation Framework (RNIF)
Web Services Flow Language (WSFL)
Wf-XML
WS Choreography Description Language (CDL)
Web Services Choreography Interface (WSCI)
Web Services Conversation Language (WSCL)
Business Process Modeling Initiative (BPMI.org)
Data Center Markup Language (DCML) Interest Group
Distributed Management Task Force (DMTF)
electronic business using eXtensible Markup Language (ebXML)
Information Technology Research and Standardization Center (INSTAC)
Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF)
Java Community Process (JCP)
Liberty Alliance Project
Object Management Group (OMG)
Open Applications Group, Inc. (OAGi)
Open Geospatial Consortium (OGC)
The Open Group
Organization for the Advancement of Structured Information Standards (OASIS)
RosettaNet
Web Services Interoperability Organization (WS-I)
Workflow Management Coalition (WfMC)
World Wide Web Consortium (W3C)
Alliance for Telecommunications Industry Solutions (ATIS)
Clinical Data Interchange Standards Consortium (CDISC)
FIX Protocol Limited (FPL)
HR-XML Consortium
IDEAlliance
Interactive Financial eXchange Forum (IFX Forum)
International Press Telecommunications Council (IPTC)
International Swaps and Derivatives Association (ISDA)
Meat & Poultry Data Standards Organization (mpXML)
Mortgage Industry Standards Maintenance Organization (MISMO)
National Information Exchange Model (NIEM)
Open Financial Exchange (OFX) Consortium
The OpenTravel Alliance (OTA)
Parlay Group
Petroleum Industry Data Exchange (PIDX)
PSLX Consortium
Real Estate Transaction Standard (RETS)
RIXML.org
Software & Information Industry Association (SIIA)
SWIFT
Individual Contributing Organizations
Academia Sinica Computing Centre (ASCC)
BEA (acquired by Oracle)
Chemistry Industry Data eXchange (CIDX)
Health Level Seven (HL7)
InterNational Committee for Information Technology Standards (INCITS)
The International Imaging Industry Association (I3A)
United Nations Centre for Trade Facilitation and Electronic Business (UN/CEFACT)
Service-Oriented Architecture (SOA) Governance
Prior Service-Oriented Architecture Specifications
DCOM
CORBA
Object Request Broker (ORB)
OMG Interface Definition Language (IDL)
Software as a Service (SaaS)
Communications as a Service (CaaS)
Platform as a Service (PaaS)
Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)
Network as a Service (NaaS)
Cloud Computing Governance
Cloud Computing FAQ
What is Cloud Bursting?
What is Cloud Washing?
Why Are There So Many "as a Service" Offerings?
eXtensible Resource Identifier (XRI)
eXtensible Stylesheet Language (XSL)
XML Path Language (XPath)
XSL Formatting Objects (XSL-FO)
XSL Transformations (XSLT)
Ink XML
REgular LAnguage description for XML (RELAX)
RELAX NG
Schematron
Synchronized Multimedia Integration Language (SMIL)
Tree Regular Expression for XML (TREX)
Voice XML
XForms
XML Linking Language (XLink)
XML Base
XML Namespaces
XML Pointer Language (XPointer)
XML Query (XQuery)
Open Applications Group Integration Specification (OAGIS)
Open Office XML
Topic Maps XML
Trade XML
Translation XML
Universal Business Language (UBL)
Universal Data Element Framework (UDEF)
Container-Managed Persistence (CMP)
Bean-Managed Persistence (BMP)
J2EE Application Program Interfaces (APIs)
Java Data Objects (JDO)
JDO PersistenceManager
JDO Identity Models
JDO Query Language (JDOQL)
Object-Oriented Database Management System (OODBMS) Definition
Stanford Linear Accelerator (SLAC)
Real Time Event Engine
Object Database Problems?
Why Use SQL Instead of an OODBMS?
Leaving the Data in a Relational Database and Using an Object Database
Consulting: Research, Analysis, and Customized Working Sessions
